{
    "subject": "resource/S\u00f8rum",
    "predicate": "property/capital",
    "object": "resource/S\u00f8rumsand",
    "human_readable": "S\u00f8rumsand is the capital of S\u00f8rum.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9460736513137817,
            "question": "Is S\u00f8rumsand a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9347725510597229,
            "question": "What is the capital of S\u00f8rum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7670065760612488,
            "question": "What is the history of S\u00f8rumsand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.701565146446228,
            "question": "Where is S\u00f8rum located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6068589687347412,
            "question": "What is the population of S\u00f8rumsand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5946864485740662,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about S\u00f8rumsand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.574953019618988,
            "question": "Does S\u00f8rumsand have any notable landmarks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5351791381835938,
            "question": "Is there anything unique about S\u00f8rumsand compared to other cities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4579606354236603,
            "question": "What administrative unit does S\u00f8rumsand belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3737125098705292,
            "question": "How would you describe S\u00f8rumsand in a few words?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=S\u00f8rumsand is the capital of S\u00f8rum.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7064_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What administrative unit does S\u00f8rumsand belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7064_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything unique about S\u00f8rumsand compared to other cities?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7064_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does S\u00f8rumsand have any notable landmarks?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7064_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7064_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents do not mention anything about S\u00f8rumsand being the capital of S\u00f8rum. In fact, one document mentions that S\u00f8rumsand is a small railway town situated in S\u00f8rum Municipality in Akershus in Norway, which suggests that S\u00f8rumsand is likely a part or a component of S\u00f8rum Municipality, rather than its capital."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nThe documents do not contain any information supporting the claim that S\u00f8rumsand is the capital of S\u00f8rum Municipality, nor does it state or imply that S\u00f8rumsand is the capital. The context provided only mentions that S\u00f8rumsand is a small railway town in S\u00f8rum Municipality, Akershus, Norway."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}